{
    "subject": "Chan_Hung-lit",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Angela_Pan",
    "human_readable": "Chan Hung-lit is married to Angela Pan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8976398706436157,
            "question": "To whom is Angela Pan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8904271125793457,
            "question": "What can you say about the relationship between Chan Hung-lit and Angela Pan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.889767587184906,
            "question": "Who is Chan Hung-lit married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8805299401283264,
            "question": "Can you describe the marital bond between Chan Hung-lit and Angela Pan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8427259922027588,
            "question": "Is Angela Pan currently married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7008692026138306,
            "question": "Is Chan Hung-lit in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.671515703201294,
            "question": "What is the name of Angela Pan's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5770148038864136,
            "question": "What is Chan Hung-lit's marital status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18320366740226746,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in this marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1718580722808838,
            "question": "Who are the partners in this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chan Hung-lit is married to Angela Pan.",
            "html": "yago_17427_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the individuals involved in this marriage?",
            "html": "yago_17427_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Chan Hung-lit's marital status?",
            "html": "yago_17427_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Angela Pan's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_17427_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17427_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Chan Hung-lit and Angela Pan were married, but they divorced in 1980.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided in the documents mentions that Angela Pan was married to actor Chan Hung-lit, also known as Chen Hung-Lit. This confirms that the statement \"Chan Hung-lit is married to Angela Pan\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Text 1 states that Pan married Chan Hung-lit in 1972 but they divorced in 1980.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}